{
    "id": "de45e161049d43bf9c3679f9eebe9511",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns And Adverbs",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The town ………………….. I was born is not far from here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "which",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "That is the office in …………….. I used to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "which",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ………………… Winston Churchill was born.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know ………………. she is from?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house in ………………… my daughter was born.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I will never forget the day on ………………..  I first met Jane.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "when",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ………………… I live.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "where"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Do you know a shop ……………… I can find toys?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "where",
                "there",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Does anybody know the reason for ……………… she hates me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is somebody ……………….. I really can’t stand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}